>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果我们不谈论诺尔斯和我们的定义，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If we're not talking
about Knowles and undefines, but
我们讨论的是弦，数字和 Booleans，这里有一种普遍的感觉
we're talking about strings, numbers and
Booleans, there's a prevailing sense here,
从草案第 4 条到第 7 条
from clauses four through seven,
that essentially,
此算法更倾向于进行数字比较。
this algorithm prefers to
do numeric comparison.
你会注意到有四个不同的地方它叫这两个号码
You'll notice four different
places it calls the two number.
上面说 X 类型是数字，但另一个是字符串，
It says if the type X is number,
but the other one is string,
然后在字符串上调用两个数字，这样我就可以进行数字比较。
then call two number on the string,
so I can do a numeric comparison.
五个都一样六次都一样
Same thing in five, same thing in six.
如果其中一个是布尔值，请在其中执行两个数字，然后进行比较。
If one of them's Boolean, then do a two
number on it, and make the comparison.
因此，它倾向于将所有内容减少到数字，以进行比较。
So it prefers to reduce everything down
to numbers to make the comparison.
现在你可能不喜欢这个算法的运作方式
Now you may not like that that's
the way the algorithm works, but
只要知道它能帮助你了解这些行为
just by knowing that it helps you
to understand the behaviors and
预测双等号算法的行为。
predict the behaviors of
the double equals algorithm.
在某些情况下你认为发生了一件事
That in some cases you thought
one thing was happening, but
实际上是完全不同的事情发生了
actually an entirely different
thing was happening.
而不是两个字符串得到比较，而是两个数字比较。
Instead of two strings getting compared,
it's two numbers getting compared.
只知道你的头在后面是平等的比较喜欢数字比较。
Just knowing in the back of your head
double equals prefers numeric comparison.
这一事实将您与所有 JavaScript 开发人员的 99.99% 隔开，
That one fact separates you from
99.99% of all JavaScript developers,
他们甚至都没看过规格
cuz they've never even read the spec.
那么我们怎么看呢 ?
So how do we see that playing out?
如果我有个数字
Well, if I have a string on a number,
就像我在网上一样，也是一个数字和网络，是一个字符串。
like I am on line one, that's a number and
online too, it's a string.
如果我重三等当然我得强迫
If I do a triple equals, of course,
I'm gonna have to forcibly make
要做一个比较，就必须是同一类型的。
the numbers to do a comparison,
they're gonna have to be the same type.
如果我有三等同等性的，它们是不同的类型，总是会失败的。
If I had a triple equals and they were
different types, it's always gonna fail.
所以我得去做数字
So I'm gonna have to make numbers.
但如果我知道只能是数字或字符串，特别是其中一个是
But if I know there can only be number or
string, especially if one of them is
一定是一个数字，就跟我最后一个的一样
definitely a number, then an exactly
the same way as I allow this with the last
东西标志，几个面前，为什么不允许双等号，
things sign, several sides ago,
why not also allow with the double equals,
为什么不这样说这个网上的这个代码是不必要的
why not say that this code online for
is more noisy unnecessarily so
这两个人的抽象概念在这里很有帮助
and the abstraction of the double
equals it's helpful here.
说他们是个数字还是
It's saying whether they're a number or
一个字符串，让它们互相比较。
a string,
let's let them compare to each other.
如果他们是平等的，伟大的，如果不是，那么伟大。
And if they're equal,
great, and if not, great.
但是，使用工具的抽象。
But use the abstraction of the tools.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我可以这样做，因为我设计了此特定功能或
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I can do this because
I designed this particular function or
这条特定的代码限制了类型
this particular piece of
code to restrict the types,
说这里唯一可以考虑的类型
to say that the only types here
that can be considered for
相等比较是字符串和数字。
the equality comparison are the string and
the number.
如果我允许数组和值，那么这将是一个更复杂的代码。
This would be a significantly more
complex code if I would allow arrays and
物体和恶霸以及各种类型的其他类型来进行对比。
objects and bullions and all kinds of
other types to come into that comparison.
所以我一直做的就是
So the case that I keep making is,
您可以选择以这种方式使用强制方式来构造代码，并且
you can choose to structure your code in
such a way that coercion is a useful and
明显的系统，而不是一些人感觉的复杂魔术。
obvious system, rather than the complex
magic that some people feel.
它把它带回了一个合理而实际的领域
It brings it back within the realm
of reasonable and practical for
你的密码基础
your code basis.
不仅是为了你还有你的所有成员
Not just for you, but for
all the members of your development.
>> 演讲者 2: 在这两种情况下，数字强度都有可能爆炸，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Look, numerical strengths
in both cases, they could blow up,
是吧
wouldn't they?
这并不是两个数字的优势，比如论坛。
It wasn't both numerical
strengths like from forum.
>> Kyle Simpson: 如果两者都是字符串，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
if they were both strings,
让我们回去思考这个算法
let's go back to thinking
about the algorithm.
如果两者都是字符串，算法会做什么 ?
If both of them were strings,
what does the algorithm do?
>> 扬声器 2: 传输数字。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Transmit the numbers.
>> Kyle Simpson: Nope，如果两者都是字符串，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Nope,
if they are both strings,
这意味着它们都是同一类型的，那么算法是做什么的呢 ?
that means they are both of the same type,
then what does the algorithm do?
>> 扬声器 3: 它执行三重等号。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It does the triple equals.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这三大平等。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It
does the triple equals.
所以我对你的回应就是如果这些字符串完全相同你会得到真实的
So my response to you is, if those strings
were literally identical, you'd get true,
否则你不会的
and otherwise you wouldn't.
但你做的每一串都是一样的
But that's the same for
every string that you do.
你不能合理地期待一个由 3.7 和一个字符串组成的字符串。
You couldn't reasonably expect a string
that said 3.7 and a string that said.
3.07 彼此相等，这些字符串是相等的，而这些数字是学习的。
3.07 to equal each other, those strings
are equal and those numbers learn.
>> 扬声器 2: 与一些在前面的输出库中输入的表单一样，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Like a form input that
some outputs base in front of it,
例如，它们变得很奇怪，但如果它是前面的空间的一个数字。
for example, they become weird but
if it's a number about the space in front.
>> Kyle Simpson: 再次，让我们重新回到上下文中，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Again,
let's reset back to the context,
当类型不同时，双等号将允许进行强制。
the double equals is going to allow
coercion when the types are different.
如果您处于不同类型的场景中，
If you're in a scenario where
the types are not different,
如果类型相同，那么它就永远不会调用强制了，永远不会。
where the types are the same, then it's
not ever going to invoke coercion, ever.
如果您想要其他其他行为，
If you want some other
additional behavior,
你所希望的不是胁迫
the thing that you want
is not coercion here,
您想要的是字符串修剪或字符串格式或类似的内容。
the thing you want is string trimming, or
string formatting or something like that.
如果您有一个案例，其中有两个字符串可能具有
If you have a case where you
have two strings that could have
在任何一方的空格里，你真的只在乎两者之间的关系。
whitespace on either side, and you really
only care about the stuff in between.
太好了这件事有个办法叫做弦切
Great, there's a thing for that and
it's called string trimming.
但那不是胁迫
But that isn't coercion.
当我有一个字符串和一个数字的时候
Coercion is when I have a string and
a number, and
我希望那些能被比较的人
I'd like those to be
compared to each other.
有什么帮助吗
Does that help?
>> 演讲者 2: 是的，是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, yeah.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, all right.
回到我们的算法最后部分第 8 课
So back to our algorithm,
the final part, classes 8 and
9，如果你用的是一个不是已经很原始的东西，
9, if you use a double equals with
something that's not already a primitive,
猜猜我们将我们的朋友调至原始人
guess what we invoke our
friend to primitive.
我们调用两个原始抽象操作。
We invoke the two primitive
abstract operation.
我们已经研究过了
We already looked at that.
记住这就是所谓的两弦或任何东西的价值。
Remember that's the one that calls
value over two string or whatever.
这里的外卖只相当于比较图元。
The takeaway here is that double
equals only compares primitives.
如果你用它不是一个原始的东西，它会怎么做 ?
If you use it with something that's
not a primitive, what's it gonna do?
把它变成一个原始的
Turn it into a primitive.
唯一不原始的事情就是当他们是一模一样的
The only time it does something with non
primitives is when they're the exact same
类型，然后仅执行相同的值三重相等比较。
type and then it just does the same
value triple equals comparison.
否则它说听着
Otherwise, it says, listen,
我现在唯一关心的强制措施就是让你成为一个原始的人
the only coercion step I care about right
now is getting you to be a primitive.
然后，我们将重新考虑该图元是否为同一类型。
And then we'll reconsider whether the
primitives are at the same type or not.
记得我刚才说的
Remember how I said earlier in the course,
这些算法本质上是递归的
that these algorithms are sorta
inherently recursive.
双等号运算符说我得把它弄明白
The double equals operator says,
I need to get it to the point,
其中一个子句匹配。
where one of these clauses matches.
如果你给我点不匹配的场景
If you give me some scenario where
it doesn't match completely,
然后我就会重新运行算法
then I'm gonna re-run
the algorithm over and over and
再重复一次，直到我找到两个属于同一类型的图元。
over again, until I get it down to two
primitives that are of the same type.
或者两个可以被强迫相等的原语。
Or two primitives that can be
coercively equal to each other.
如果我没找到这一点，你猜是什么，假的，他们不平等。
And if I never get to that point,
guess what, false, they are not equal.
换句话说，我们会调用这两个原语并获取两个原语，并且
So in other words, we would invoke the two
primitive and get two primitives, and
然后用我们的两个原语返回算法
then come back to the algorithm
with our two primitives, and
然后做出相应的决定。
then make the decision accordingly.